On the way.
>> On the way to the White House.
>> Wow, look at this, Emma.
>> Let's get ready to go to the White House
today.
>> There's Christmas music blaring right
now.
[cheering]
>> All right. Well, what's up vlog? Um,
right now I'm heading to Alex, but this
is a big vlog, guys. Like huge vlog.
This is the White House Christmas vlog,
which is insane because it's like very
special. Not many people get to do it.
So, tomorrow, my family and I are going
on a plane to the White House to
literally just fly there for the day,
film whatever. It's like a Christmas
party, and then come back home. I'm
looking forward to it. It's always nice
going to the White House, especially
this time of year. It's like, it's
awesome with like the seasons and
everything, but should be fun. I'm
taking you guys along. Having my coffee
this morning. go to see Alex, too.
[music] Get a little quick workout in.
Um, and um, yeah,
that's it. I'm pretty tired. I have Alex
today. Um, and then I am I have my uh,
dentist today as well as um, another
doctor's appointment I got to go to. But
let's make a coffee because I am tired.
Look at these bags.
I was really hoping my mom has food.
Looks like I just need to do coffee in
here.
Oh my god. She got a she got she got us
a hot hot um cider.
It's awesome.
>> [screaming]
>> We're also getting some protein intake
cuz I don't know. Low key feeling I'm
coming out with something.
Put this in my life.
All right, guys. I also lowkey might go
to Best Buy today and buy another
camera. This camera is awesome. It's
good, but I also want a camera that has
some flash on it that I could also take
photos and vlog with. You know what I
mean? So, like a little bit of both. So,
that's what I might be doing today.
[snorts]
Got our ground beef. Got our coffee.
Let's see what syrups I want today. My
mom bought me this.
Vanilla creme brulee.
I asked this for my Christmas list, too.
Some of the stuffs I've got for my
Christmas like I asked for my my list.
My mom been just like leaving them out
and I think she thinks I'm ordering them
even though like she's the one who
ordered them. So like all my like like
coffee syrups that I got for um
Christmas, she just put them like in a
syrup box. like she didn't even like
wrap them or anything like that.
I mean, I'm 18 years old. I guess when
you get to turn it, you just like
whatever.
I should do like two servings of the
serum. I like when my coffee does not
taste like coffee. And some coconut
milk.
Two oranges,
some beer,
and coffee.
Coffee test.
Wow. So good. All right. I'm bring this
number you guys.
All right. I'm going to eat. I'll see
you guys soon. Oh, wait. Let me show you
what it looks like.
All right, guys. So, pretty much I
actually found my old camera, which is
crazy. My old camera with my old
vlogging clips when I was like 8 years
old. No, I was probably close age. I was
probably like 11ish.
I found the old clips of me vlogging
when I was 11 years old, which is
actually so funny. I might put like
together like a video of like recapping
of like my year and whatever, like a
kind of like a year rewind type of
thing. Um, and I got those clips in. Um,
but I thought it was really funny
because it's like found my old clips. I
don't know. So, we got big things. I did
find out I did find a dress. My mom's
like I think debating between like two
dresses. So, let me go help her out
later today to like decide which one she
thinks is better. And also, yesterday I
got into University of Miami like
officially. Also, he says I'm an
athlete, it's like a little different.
So, like you commit, you meet the
coaches, you commit whatever. And then
eventually, yeah, you have to like apply
like a regular prime student in a way.
But I applied I got in yesterday, so
that was cool. Some of my friends got in
as well, which is nice. So, yep. And
I'll see you guys in the next clip. Oh,
it's really bright.
>> All right, guys. We're We're with Alex.
Trist got Tristan in the gym.
>> Yeah. There you go. There you go.
>> Oh, yeah. Big T.
>> There you go. Knees forward.
>> Look, you're you're like sitting down on
the toilet, Tristan.
>> That's you.
>> What?
>> Feet forward.
>> Squat.
What
>> do we start with and then we go
>> we go resets and then we go through
that. So what
>> we do resets
>> which is your rolling stuff
>> and then box jumps and then we
[music]
>> I just my dentist see really white. Now
I'm going through a car wash.
Emma's going to be so jealous. I'm going
through a car wash without powder.
She gets like jealous. There's a lot
going on. So car wash time.
Um yeah, the dentist is really good. I
have fun.
I also need like the inside.
I don't want to do that. I might just be
like get detailed inside. It's not bad.
It's not terrible.
[music]
I'll see you when I'm back.
So, now I'm at Emma's house with Big
Brad, Emma, and Bella. We're doing a
video for Emma's channel. As you guys
have seen, I have had a very busy day.
Look at my teeth.
So nice and white.
>> OH, WOW. WOW.
>> YOU AND I YOU AND I ARE sharing a
couple.
>> Wow. Look at this, Emma.
>> I was going to DO THIS, TOO.
>> YES, it
>> Oh, yes.
>> These are mine, right?
>> Yes, cuz
I approve of them. I took most of them
from your repost and then some of them I
just like remember you calling hot.
These are all very valid.
>> OH MY GOD, BRO. No way. I got I got
Guys, hear me out on hear me out,
though. Look at this one. Look, Bella's
got the Quaker Oats guy in there.
Actually, don't even show her. Just let
her see it.
>> No, bro. Hey, this is
>> You guys are going to have to see Kai's
reaction on my channel. Real Mark.
>> No, no. [laughter]
>> The real Mark. Oh my god. Wait.
Invisible Man from Waltz, Transsylvania.
The
>> I knew you were GOING TO PUT THAT. I
KNEW YOU WERE GOING TO PUT THE GLASSES.
I KNEW you were going to put I have a
thing for these types of glasses.
>> You stop lying, KAI. WAIT, WHERE'S I
WANT TO PUT THIS ONE, TOO.
>> YES. [screaming] OH MY GOD.
>> YOU GUYS ARE LIKE the mental ill, bro.
Let spill yours. Emma's show.
So fun.
>> No, not at all.
>> WAIT, SHOULD WE LET tell her about some
of these suicide squads?
>> I'm going to hide the rest of them. Some
of THESE ARE LIKE REALLY [laughter]
REALLY FAT. MR. Clean
>> Cat Noir. She might not KNOW THAT.
>> THIS ONE CAUGHT ME OFF GUARD.
>> ARE your Are you killed that one?
>> Are your cake almost done?
>> What?
>> What do you mean is the cake almost
done?
>> WHERE'S THE CAKE?
>> HI.
>> WAIT, HOW the cake?
>> Oh, you got cake.
>> All right, let's start making the cake.
>> All right, they charged.
>> Kind of taught me how to apply this
earlier.
>> Oh, you like my mic.
Guys, should I get Emma's camera? I
lowkey want to go best.
>> I like my camera.
>> Who wants to go best? You want to come
look at our setup for the video?
>> Yeah. I want to see how I actually want
to see the I actually Can I see the raw
film when you're done with this? Just to
look.
>> Are they on and connected?
>> Um, yeah.
>> Yes,
>> they are.
>> Wait, you're going to get one and then
me and Bella.
>> You do have great quality, guys. The
upgraded lens I bought is actually
blurrier than the the default lens. You
got to play.
>> All right. Can I get back here?
>> All right. Wait. I have to go now. Bye,
everyone. I have to go now.
>> All right, guys.
>> Let's get ready to go to the White House
today. Um, today's the day. It's the
Christmas party. I'm getting ready now.
Let's have a fun day.
The setting. It's not even an ad, but I
I literally use this every day.
When I put my contacts in, it literally
looks like I'm crying. Put this like
right here.
Makeup,
guys. So, I was with Michaela yesterday
and [music] Michaela told me that I
totally put my makeup on wrong, but it
always looks so good. And I don't know
how I do wrong. Like, I feel like this
is like the only way to do it. So, what
do you guys think?
Guys, I'm sure with the weather that my
skin's going to like start cracking.
It's 14°.
Oh, that's what I saw. 14. I don't know
if it's still 14. I hope [music] that
would suck.
Be right back.
Right. So, this is the final product.
Doesn't look bad. I'm going to put my
clothes on though and I'm going to do my
hair just so like I don't like mess up
all this or actually so I don't mess my
hair. That's why. I'll see you guys
soon.
It's a straight
because I got layers. It looks so weird
now.
It does not
One minute.
>> All right.
I take this brush away.
All right.
You guys leave me chat. I'll see you
guys soon. [music]
All right, guys. So, we just got to the
airport like um aviation like [music]
place and now we're going to walk to the
plane with everyone.
>> All right, guys. We're on the plane
right now um with everyone. And um yeah,
there's Christmas music blaring right
now.
I'm going to go in the front for
takeoff. Okay, go.
>> All right, we're on the plane now.
Set time.
[music]
>> [music]
>> Heat. Heat.
[music]
Was
that cool?
>> Was that cool?
>> Yeah.
>> All right, guys. So, we just changed
into this really basic outfit, but
whatever. Yeah,
>> we're almost over. We're landing soon in
like 15 minutes or so.
>> All right, guys. So, now we're in the
car
>> on the way
>> on the way to the White House.
I took this from the east. This came out
of the east. The famous east. But this
looks good. Really?
>> How about the gold?
>> Same man that did the Mount Rushmore.
>> The gold looks nice. You added that.
>> Very nice.
[music] Guys,
[music]
I'm literally running back to the old
office right now. I forgot my purse.
Watch out. It's like black ice right
over there.
Yes.
Hey, [music] how are you? Nice to see
you. Good to see you,
>> Santa.
Good. Let's walk around and take a
photo.
[music]
Okay guys, we're we're sitting in the
bedroom right now. Um and um all
drinking hot chocolate. And if there's
like a hot chocolate bar where like you
make your own hot chocolate.
>> Yeah, but you need to make a video of
it.
>> Why don't you make another one? Do you
want another one
>> later?
>> On the way on the on the way to the
airport. Another one. Oh, you got a
spoon.
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, where were the spoons?
>> Literally right there at home right now.
>> I like to say that was because of the
November 5th election. You're the
longest, straightest hitter that putts
the best and chips the best. Typically,
you're going to do quite well. And he
does. Come on up here. Say hello.
And he current US Open champion.
[cheering]
>> All right.
>> Well, I did not know I was going to be
coming up here today, but uh I got to
say thank you and what the president
done.
All right, guys. Well, I hope you guys
enjoyed the White House Christmas vlog.
Um, there's going to be another
Christmas vlog when um it's actually
Christmas with my family and whatnot,
but I hope you guys enjoyed that one.
It's obviously very special and I'm very
lucky to go there and everything like
that. Um, make sure you guys like and
subscribe and hit the notification
button for the next videos and I always
post every Saturday. So, see you guys in
the next one. Bye.
[music]